SAGAR SHRESTHA

• DETAILS •

+977-9860332656 saagarshrest@gmail.com

• LINKS •

www.saagarshrest.com

www.dribbble.com/saagarshrest

www.Lottiefiles.com/saagarshrest

www.linkedin.com/in/saagarshrest

o SKILLS o

Figma

Interaction Design

Prototyping

Balsamiq

Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere Pro

2D Animation

JSON animation / lottie

Adobe Photoshop

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Nepali

PROFILE

User Interface/Experience Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Adobe Softwares like XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects, Premier Pro, Audition, Indesign, etc, also softwares like Figma, Invison, WordPress. Strong knowledge of aesthetic Designing skills, along with 2D Animation, Digital Marketing and Management

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

UI/UX Designer at Infinity Digital Agency, Kathmandu

November 2021 — Present

- Gathering data and user requirements based on research and collaboration with client and product managers.
- · Creating storyboard, user process flows.
- · Designing wireframes based on UX.
- · Creating high fidelity UI designs.
- Adding Interaction design and prototyping that demonstrates how the design and product functions,
- Identifying and troubleshooting UX problems.

UI/UX Designer at Dreamax.co.il (Remote), Israel

September 2021 — November 2021

- Conducting User flow research.
- Designing high fidelity UI for platform.
- UX research to create no coding web development builder.
- · Working with developers to solve design issues

Senior UI/UX Designer at Bitsbeat, Kathmandu

July 2020 — May 2021

- Gathering data and user requirements based on research and collaboration with client and product managers.
- Creating storyboard, user process flows.
- Designing wireframes based on UX.
- Creating high fidelity UI designs.
- Adding Interaction design and prototyping that demonstrates how the design and product functions,
- · Identifying and troubleshooting UX problems.
- Conducting training and tutoring interns.
- Guiding juniors in their design process.
- · Creating 2D animation for website and videos

Designer at Braindigit, Kathmandu

May 2019 — April 2020

 Gathering data and user requirements based on research and collaboration with client and product managers.

- Managing the team to get the job done and create creative content.
- Designing Game UI based on subject requirement.
- Adding Interaction design and prototyping that demonstrates how the design and product functions,
- Identifying and troubleshooting UX problems.
- · Conducting training and tutoring interns.
- Guiding juniors in their design process.
- Creating 2D animation for website and videos

Designer at Floyd Consultancy, Kathmandu

September 2018 — January 2019

- Gathering data and user requirements based on research and collaboration with client and product managers.
- Designing product based on client requirement.
- Guiding juniors in their design process.
- Creating designs for web, mobile and physical product.

Designer at Blackspring, Kathmandu

January 2016 — August 2018

- Creating website design.
- Working with wordpress theme design.
- · Mobile app design.
- · App icon and Logo design.

EDUCATION

9 EMBA, Purbanchal University, Kathmandu

COURSES

Ask Question to Make Data Driven Decisions, Google

January 2022

Foundation: Data, Data, Everywhere, Google

June 2021

The Fundamental of Digital Marketing, Google

July 2018

■ REFERENCES

References available upon request